<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!--Generated by PAR5E - Fantasy Grounds Module Parser - Zeus Copyright 2014-->
<root version="3.0">
  <tables />
  <referenceSW5EPHB static="true">
    <backgrounddata>
      <agent>
        <name type="string">Agent</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p>Many organizations active in the galaxy aren't bound by strictures of geography. These factions pursue their agendas without regard for political boundaries, and their members operate anywhere the organization deems necessary. These groups employ listeners, rumormongers, smugglers, mercenaries, cache-holders (people who guard caches of wealth or items for use by the faction's operatives), haven keepers, and message drop minders, to name a few. At the core of every faction are those who don't merely fulfill a small function for that organization, but who serve as its hands, head, and heart. As a prelude to your adventuring career (and in preparation for it), you served as an agent of a particular faction. You might have operated openly or secretly, depending on the faction and its goals, as well as how those goals mesh with your own. Becoming an adventurer doesn't necessarily require you to relinquish membership in your faction (though you can choose to do so), and it might enhance your status in the faction.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skills</b> Choose two from Deception, Investigation, Lore, and Persuasion</p><h>Languages</h><p>Two of your choice</p><h>Equipment</h><p>Badge or emblem of your faction, a copy of a seminal faction text (or a code-book for a covert faction), a set of common clothes, and a pouch containing 150 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skills type="string">Choose two from Deception, Investigation, Lore, and Persuasion</skills>
        <languages type="string">Two of your choice</languages>
        <equipment type="string">Badge or emblem of your faction, a copy of a seminal faction text (or a code-book for a covert faction), a set of common clothes, and a pouch containing 150 cr</equipment>
      </agent>
      <barbarian>
        <name type="string">Barbarian</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p>Though you might have only recently arrived in civilized lands, you are no stranger to the values of cooperation and group effort when striving for supremacy. You learned these principles, and much more, as a member of your tribe.</p><p>Your people have always tried to hold to the old ways. Tradition and taboo have kept your tribe strong while the kingdoms of others have collapsed into chaos and ruin. But for the last few generations, some bands among the tribes were tempted to settle, make peace, trade, and even to build towns. Perhaps this is why your tribe chose to raise up the totems among the people as living embodiments of his power. Perhaps they needed a reminder of who they were and from whence they came. The Chosen of your tribe led bands back to the old ways, and most of your people abandoned the soft ways of civilization.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skills</b> Choose two from Animal Handling, Athletics, Nature, and Survival</p><p><b>Tools</b> One type of musical instrument or artisan's tools</p><h>Languages</h><p>One of your choice</p><h>Equipment</h><p>A hunting trap, a totemic token or set of tattoos marking your loyalty to your tribe, a set of traveler's clothes, and a pouch containing 100 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skills type="string">Choose two from Animal Handling, Athletics, Nature, and Survival</skills>
        <tools type="string">One type of musical instrument or artisan's tools</tools>
        <languages type="string">One of your choice</languages>
        <equipment type="string">A hunting trap, a totemic token or set of tattoos marking your loyalty to your tribe, a set of traveler's clothes, and a pouch containing 100 cr</equipment>
      </barbarian>
      <bountyhunter>
        <name type="string">Bounty Hunter</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p><b>Before you became an adventurer, your life was already full of conflict and excitement, because you made a living tracking down people for pay. Unlike some people who collect bounties, though, you aren't a savage who follows quarry into or through the wilderness. You're involved in a lucrative trade, in the place where you live, that routinely tests your skills and survival instincts. What's more, you aren't alone, as a bounty hunter in the wild would be</b>:  you routinely interact with both the criminal subculture and other bounty hunters, maintaining contacts in both areas to help you succeed.</p><p>You might be a cunning thief-catcher, prowling the rooftops to catch one of the myriad burglars of the city. Perhaps you are someone who has your ear to the street, aware of the doings of street gangs. You might be a \"velvet mask\" bounty hunter, one who blends in with high society and noble circles in order to catch the criminals that prey on the rich, whether pickpockets or con artists. As a member of an adventuring party, you might find it more difficult to pursue a personal agenda that doesn't fit with the group's objectives - but on the other hand, you can take down much more formidable targets with the help of your companions.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skills</b> Choose two from Deception, Insight, Persuasion, and Stealth</p><p><b>Tool Proficiencies</b> Your choice of demolitions kit, security kit, or slicer's kit</p><h>Languages</h><p>One of your choice</p><h>Equipment</h><p>A set of clothes appropriate to your duties, a set of binders, and a pouch containing 200 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skills type="string">Choose two from Deception, Insight, Persuasion, and Stealth</skills>
        <toolproficiencies type="string">Your choice of demolitions kit, security kit, or slicer's kit</toolproficiencies>
        <languages type="string">One of your choice</languages>
        <equipment type="string">A set of clothes appropriate to your duties, a set of binders, and a pouch containing 200 cr</equipment>
      </bountyhunter>
      <citywatch>
        <name type="string">City Watch</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p>You have served the community where you grew up, standing as its first line of defense against crime and wildlife. You aren't a soldier, directing your gaze outward at possible enemies. Instead, your service to your hometown was to help police its populace, protecting the citizenry from lawbreakers and malefactors of every stripe.</p><p>Even if you're not city-born or city-bred, this background can describe your early years as a member of law enforcement. Most settlements of any size have their own law enforcement forces.</p><p><b>Feature</b>:  Watcher's Eye</p><p>Your experience in enforcing the law, and dealing with lawbreakers, gives you a feel for local laws and criminals. You can easily find the local outpost of the watch or a similar organization, and just as easily pick out the dens of criminal activity in a community, although you're more likely to be welcome in the former locations rather than the latter.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skills</b> Choose two from Athletics, Insight, Investigation, and Perception</p><h>Languages</h><p>Two of your choice</p><h>Equipment</h><p>A uniform in the style of your unit and indicative of your rank, a horn with which to summon help, a set of binders, and a pouch containing 100 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skills type="string">Choose two from Athletics, Insight, Investigation, and Perception</skills>
        <languages type="string">Two of your choice</languages>
        <equipment type="string">A uniform in the style of your unit and indicative of your rank, a horn with which to summon help, a set of binders, and a pouch containing 100 cr</equipment>
      </citywatch>
      <clonetrooper>
        <name type="string">Clone Trooper</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p>You are one of millions; genetically engineered, identical specimens designed to be the perfect soldier. Created from a template provided by the legendary bounty hunter Jango Fett, you represent the latest and greatest evolution in galactic warfare.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skills</b> Choose two from Athletics, Medicine, Perception, and Piloting</p><p><b>Tools</b> Your choice of demolitions kit, security kit, or slicer's kit</p><h>Languages</h><p>One of your choice</p><h>Equipment</h><p>Badge or emblem of your rank, your chosen tools, a set of common clothes, and a pouch containing 100 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skills type="string">Choose two from Athletics, Medicine, Perception, and Piloting</skills>
        <tools type="string">Your choice of demolitions kit, security kit, or slicer's kit</tools>
        <languages type="string">One of your choice</languages>
        <equipment type="string">Badge or emblem of your rank, your chosen tools, a set of common clothes, and a pouch containing 100 cr</equipment>
      </clonetrooper>
      <courtier>
        <name type="string">Courtier</name>
        <text type="formattedtext"><p>In your earlier days, you were a personage of some significance in a noble court or a bureaucratic organization. You might or might not come from an upper-class family; your talents, rather than the circumstances of your birth, could have secured you this position.</p><p>You might have been one of the many functionaries, attendants, and other hangers-on in Coruscant's upper echelons, or perhaps you traveled in Nar Shaddaa's baroque and sometimes cutthroat conglomeration of guilds, nobles, adventurers, and secret societies. You might have been one of the behind-the-scenes law-keepers or functionaries on Dromund Kaas, or you might have grown up on some other affluent planet.</p><p>Even if you are no longer a full-fledged member of the group that gave you your start in life, your relationships with your former fellows can be an advantage for you and your adventuring comrades. You might undertake missions with your new companions that further the interest of the organization that gave you your start in life. In any event, the abilities that you honed while serving as a courtier will stand you in good stead as an adventurer.</p><p><b>Feature</b>:  Court Functionality</p><p>Your knowledge of how bureaucracies function lets you gain access to the records and inner workings of any noble court or government you encounter. You know who the movers and shakers are, whom to go to for the favors you seek, and what the current intrigues of interest in the group are.</p><h>Traits</h><listlink></listlink><h>Proficiencies</h><p><b>Skill Proficiencies</b> Choose two from Deception, Insight, Performance, and Survival</p><h>Languages</h><p><b>Equipment</b>:  A set of fine clothes and a pouch containing 150 cr</p></text>
        <traits />
        <skillproficiencies type="string">Choose two from Deception, Insight, Performance, and Survival</skillproficiencies>
        <languages type="string">Equipment: A set of fine clothes and a pouch containing 150 cr</languages>
      </courtier>
    </backgrounddata>
    <backgroundlists>
      <byletter>
        <description type="string">Backgrounds</description>
        <groups>
          <typeletterA>
            <description type="string">A</description>
            <index>
              <agent>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.agent@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </agent>
            </index>
          </typeletterA>
          <typeletterB>
            <description type="string">B</description>
            <index>
              <barbarian>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.barbarian@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </barbarian>
              <bountyhunter>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.bountyhunter@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </bountyhunter>
            </index>
          </typeletterB>
          <typeletterC>
            <description type="string">C</description>
            <index>
              <citywatch>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.citywatch@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </citywatch>
              <clonetrooper>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.clonetrooper@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </clonetrooper>
              <courtier>
                <link type="windowreference">
                  <class>reference_background</class>
                  <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgrounddata.courtier@SW5e</recordname>
                  <description>
                    <field>name</field>
                  </description>
                </link>
                <source type="string" />
              </courtier>
            </index>
          </typeletterC>
        </groups>
      </byletter>
    </backgroundlists>
    <refmanualdata />
    <refmanualindex>
      <chapters />
    </refmanualindex>
  </referenceSW5EPHB>
  <library>
    <libnsw5eSW5EPHB>
      <name type="string">SW5e Reference Library</name>
      <categoryname type="string">D&amp;D 5e Rule Set</categoryname>
      <entries>
        <id-00001>
          <librarylink type="windowreference">
            <class>reference_colindex</class>
            <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.backgroundlists.byletter</recordname>
          </librarylink>
          <name type="string">Backgrounds</name>
        </id-00001>
        <id-00002>
          <librarylink type="windowreference">
            <class>reference_manual</class>
            <recordname>referenceSW5EPHB.refmanualindex</recordname>
          </librarylink>
          <name type="string">Reference Manual</name>
        </id-00002>
      </entries>
    </libnsw5eSW5EPHB>
  </library>
</root>
